I…
passed the interview.
Rin.
Congratulations.
You really earned it.
Thank you.
I know that I
put you in a tough spot…
and that you thought
really hard about it for me.
I know it all.
So…
I want to treasure that no matter…
what happens.
I want to keep it safe with me…
even when I return to Korea.
If you feel lonely, don't hide it.
Okay.
You too.
I never hide it.
You know that, don't you?
That's true.
We will…
be okay.
Yeah.
CLOSED FOR PRIVATE EVENT
Picture time!
Hurry, hurry! Come on!
Closer, closer. Okay.
Okay, say
-Tanomi!
Actually, having a takoyaki party was
on my bucket list too.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-I'm glad we got to do it together.
Thanks.
They're turning perfectly round.
Yeah.
This one's burning.
Ouch!
That was hot.
Of course it's hot.
-It was my bare hand, too.
-No wonder.
Thank you.
The last time we met…
I'm sorry I was rude to you.
Oh no, it's nothing.
-You see, I told you it's hot!
-It's so hot!
Are you okay?
Shige, I want to eat one too.
Sure.
-This one?
-Rin
-needed you, it seems.
-Try this one.
Please take care of Rin from now on too.
Yes, I will.
-Jjan.
‎Rin, that one is ready to eat.
Here, Shige.
Thank you.
So when are you going back?
The 28th.
That's so soon!
I see…
It'll be lonely without you.
Sorry.
It's okay.
I'm just going to be
a little far away, that's all.
Nothing else will change.
I mean, we have social media
and video calling too.
Yeah.
Nothing will change between us.
You two will be okay.
If you love each other,
it'll be okay no matter where you are.
Right?
Shige…
Hey,
I bet you think
those were such wise words.
I do.
And so, Rin, come visit us anytime.
When you feel lonely,
you just need to come visit… me.
I will.
-You heard that?
-Oh, Shige…
-Taiga.
-Yes?
I'll give this to you.
What?
-This is… yours.
-Yeah.
Make sure you sharpen it.
Pay more attention to how you sharpen
your knife than how you cut with it.
Yes. I will use it with the utmost care.
Thank you very much.
-Um, Shige…
-Huh?
If it's not too much trouble,
may I continue working here
even when I start school?
Well, I appreciate that you want to,
but shouldn't you focus on school?
Tanomi is where my roots are.
Thanks to you, Shige, and our customers,
I am who I am today.
That's why I want to continue helping out
for as long as I can.
Well then,
maybe I will take you up on that offer.
Okay. Thank you very much.
TANOMI
HERE ARE THE PHOTOS FROM TODAY! THANK YOU!
It's already been a year, huh?
Hello?
I'm sorry. Were you sleeping?
No.
What's up?
You know…
There's a place I want to take you.
So this is where you grew up?
It's a comfortable and warm place,
just like you.
Really?
It feels strange to be here with you.
I was always practicing on my own.
I would use this as my starting line,
and run downstream.
I loved running here.
The wind, the sounds, the scents…
Everything felt amazing.
-I want to see you running.
-What?
That's embarrassing.
Come on. Just once.
Okay, let's race to that point.
There's no way you'd win.
Sijag!
You're serious?
Taiga!
Wait…
Rin?
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
But you were going so far away…
-Are you okay?
-Yeah.
Taiga is always taking care of me.
My name is Park Rin.
Oh, this is…
no… um…
It's nothing much, but please enjoy.
Oh my.
You didn't have to. Thank you.
Rin is from Korea,
and came here to study animation.
So you're going to work
in the animation field in Japan?
No.
Once I graduate,
I plan on working in Korea,
designing for an advertising company.
I see…
Is that right?
So when are you graduating?
-This month.
-What?
So this month you're going back to Korea?
Yes.
Um…
You two are dating, right?
Yes, we are.
I'm sorry for making you worried.
But we made this decision together.
We came here
because I wanted to show Rin
the place where I grew up.
I…
have a goal now, thanks to Rin.
The truth is,
I'm thinking of becoming
a registered dietitian.
So…
I'm going to school starting April.
Wait a second.
You're going back to school?
But what about the restaurant?
The owner was very understanding,
so I'm going to work
while going to school.
That's not realistic.
What if it doesn't work again--
Even if it doesn't work, again,
I'll be fine this time.
Because now I know that
I can always start again.
RENEWS HIGHEST RANKING
Taiga.
You're okay on time?
I was just thinking about
how hard I worked back then.
Thank you for having me today.
My pleasure.
Next time…
See you.
Wait.
Send me the address
of the place you're working at.
What?
They're taking care of you, right?
When I go to Tokyo,
I'll pay my respects.
Okay.
Thank you, Big Bro.
When Taiga decided to quit track,
I was anxious and worried,
so I said a lot
of unnecessary things to him.
That has always been bothering me.
I realized
that I should've had more faith in him,
and let him follow his own course.
Seeing him today made me realize that.
You and Taiga
will be able to find
what is best for the both of you.
I am sure.
Yes.
Mom, we'll have to leave soon.
-Take care, you two.
-Thanks.
Rin, please take care of Taiga.
Oh, he is always the one
taking care of me.
I…
will do my best, one step at a time.
I'm looking forward to it.
But don't overwork yourself.
GRADUATION EXHIBITION
TOKYO UNIVERSITY OF FINE ARTS
DEPARTMENT OF ANIMATION
ONIGIRI - PARK RIN
Back when I first started school,
I wanted to become an animator,
but I didn't have anything
specific in mind.
What do I want to do?
What am I capable of?
I didn't know the answer
and was completely lost.
Thinking back now,
there were moments
I compared myself to others…
and moments where I suffered
from self-doubt.
But all of those moments…
were very important detours
that I had to make, in a way.
Just to make one onigiri,
you need to cook the rice,
prepare the stuffing,
and wrap it in seaweed.
Everything is a product
of small, individual steps.
And what's important
is what kind of outlook
you have on each and every one
of those steps.
That is what I learned
over the past two years.
I hope that this animation
motivates you to cast a spotlight
on fleeting moments like these.
Thank you very much for watching.
Mom, I just returned the key.
I'll head to the airport soon.
Shall we go?
Yeah.
NARITA INTERNATIONAL AIRPORT
All right, so we'll send a message
every day when we wake up,
and we'll do a video call before bed.
These two are a must, right?
Yeah.
As soon as I can take time off,
I'll send you my schedule.
I think I can visit you
some time during summer break too.
Well then…
I guess…
we're all set?
Oh, that's right.
One final thing…
I mean, it's not "final" but…
I wanted you to eat this.
Thank you.
I'm so happy.
Thanks.
What is this called?
It's shigure-ni
with shishito peppers and beef.
Shigure-ni…
It kind of tastes like Korean jang-jorim.
I'm sorry, we're closed for today.
TANOMI
Okay…
-You eat like you really enjoy the food.
-Joesongham-- I mean, I'm sorry.
Out of all the onigiri I've had in Japan,
this is the best.
The Classic.
This is like a scene
out of my favorite movie.
-Bucket list?
-Yes.
Why don't you make one too?
When I'm with you,
I feel like I can move forward.
Taiga, are you not that good
at keeping in touch?
When you don't read my messages,
or a day goes by without a word from you,
I start to wonder
if you have no interest in me.
Happy birthday!
Why didn't you say anything?
Whatever.
Maybe it is difficult for two people
from different backgrounds to be together?
From now on…
I want to know more about
the things you value.
Thank you.
I believe
that your training right now
will not be wasted.
Just like you said,
if we try our best to share
everything with each other,
we won't be lonely
even if we're far apart…
I think.
Why didn't you tell me?
Well…
Were you hiding it?
Of course not.
I wish you would've accepted me,
even just for a second.
Why don't you get it?
Sorry.
I can't keep up with you.
Your words…
Your smile…
Everything about you
gave me strength.
I don't want to let you go yet.
Whether I'm feeling happy, or anything,
‎FORTUNE
the first person I think of is you.
Everything brings me back to you.
I like you, Taiga.
I want to stay with you
even after you graduate.
I want to be with you too.
Rin…
You can't stay here, right?
I'm sorry.
I didn't want to end things like this…
I mean,
I know it's not the end, but…
But you know…
I was…
saved by you.
Taiga…
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
Hello?
Hello.
-Did you eat already?
-Yeah.
What about you?
I ate.
How was your presentation?
It went well.
Did you finish your assignment on time?
I barely made it.
I'm glad.
Good work.
You too.
-Jjan.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE YOU
Happy birthday!
Rin!
-Thank you!
-Congratulations.
I missed you.
The smell comes from the oil
in between the skin and flesh.
If you cook it from the skin side first,
it starts to come out.
As the oil comes out, keep removing it
using something like a paper towel.
By doing this,
you can get rid of that smell…
TAIGA: ARE YOU GOING ANYWHERE THIS SUMMER?
Let's go.
What should we get? Beer?
-Sounds good.
-Come on!
‎VISITING A CAFE WITH A FRIEND
Excuse me.
Welcome.
Here's this month's payment.
Thank you.
Okay.
By the way, I read it.
Akki's Pachiizm.
Congrats on your first serialization.
-You're amazing, Dongsaeng!
-No, I'm not.
It took me two whole years!
Being a writer is really tough.
Hyeongnim, can I take this real quick?
Hello?
Oh, I'm so sorry!
This week I'm fully booked.
Excuse me!
Two orders of sundae gukbap
and soju please.
‎Hey!
How are you doing? Having fun?
I'm doing well.
I might be able to apply
for my second visa soon.
Ivanna!
Look, she's my roommate.
Hello. This is Shige.
I don't know what's going on,
but I'm glad to see
that you're doing well.
Yeah. Where's Taiga today?
Oh, he's pretty busy with his other job.
Their game is tomorrow,
so the menu is heavier
on the carbohydrates than usual.
And to boost the athletes' performance,
we chose
ingredients and cooking methods that
promote easier digestion and absorption.
Yes.
This is good, Taiga.
All right, let's go with this.
Okay. Let's start preparing.
-Yes.
MAMA'S SEASONAL MUST-TRY DINER
RED CHILI PASTE BULGOGI
RESTAURANT GARDEN BALAM
Over here!
You're late!
Sorry!
I'm famished. Let's hurry up and order.
What do you feel like?
-I don't know…
-It's hard, huh?
We survived another week.
-Cheers!
This is the best!
I can feel it bring
my whole body back to life!
This week was crazy, as always.
Me too.
But living a fulfilling life
is a good thing.
True.
Do you enjoy your job?
Yeah.
Please enjoy.
-Thank you.
This looks good.
You really like that, don't you?
Is it because of your ex-boyfriend?
This is amazing!
This gimbap is so good!
Thank you.
Someone special to me
taught me how to make it.
THIS DRAMA IS FICTION AND ALL CHARACTERS
AND ORGANIZATIONS ARE FICTIONAL
Subtitle translation by: Kiko Morita